Register of the William H. Rehnquist papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- U.S. Supreme Court Case Files, 1972-1974
  - 1974 October Term (October 1974 September 1975), 1974-1975
    - National Labor Relations Board v. Western Addition Community Organization (Box-folder 74: 73-830)
      Found in case 73-696
    - Jack A. Fusari, Commissioner of Labor of the State of Connecticut, Administrator, Unemployment Compensation v. Larry Steinberg (Box-folder 74: 73-848)
    - Alfredo Gonzalez, individually and on Behalf of All Others Similarly Situated v. Automatic Employment Credit Union (Box-folder 74: 73-858)
    - Cox Broadcasting Corporation v. Martin Cohn, (2 folders) (Box-folder 74: 73-938)
    - Southeastern Promotions, Ltd. v. Steve Conrad (Box-folder 74: 73-1004)
    - Gulf Oil Corporation v. Copp Paving Company, Inc. (Box-folder 74: 73-1012)
    - John Lascaris v. Sylvia Shirley (Box-folder 74: 73-1016)
      See also case 73-1095
    - United States v. Martin Dewalt Mazurie, (2 folders) (Box-folder 74, 75: 73-1018)
    - Abe Lavine v. Sylvia Shirley (Box-folder 75: 73-1095)
      Found in case 73-1016
    - William Cousins v. Paul T. Wigoda (Box-folder 75: 73-1106)
    - MTM, Inc. v. William J. Baxley (Box-folder 75: 73-1119)
    - North Georgia Finishing Inc. v. Di-Chem, Inc. (Box-folder 75: 73-1121)
    - United States v. Ralph Feola (Box-folder 75: 73-1123)
    - Cheryl Spider DeCoteau, Natural Mother and Next Friend of Robert Lee Feather and Herbert John Spider v. The District County Court for the Tenth Judicial District (Box-folder 75: 73-1148)
      See also case 73-1500
    - United States v. Thomas Joseph Wilson and Bobby Antonio Bryan (Box-folder 75: 73-1162)
    - Interstate Commerce Commission v. Oregon Pacific Industries Inc. (Box-folder 75: 73-1210)
    - Linden Lumber Division, Summer & Co. v. National Labor Relations Board (Box-folder 76: 73-1231)
      See also case 73-1234
    - National Labor Relations Board v. Sears, Roebuck & Co. (Box-folder 76: 73-1233)
    - National Labor Relations Board v. Truck Drivers Union Local 413 (Box-folder 76: 73-1234)
      Found in case 73-1231
    - United States v. Richard V. Bisceglia (Box-folder 76: 73-1245)
    - Connell Construction Company, Inc. v. Plumbers and Steamfitters Local Union 100 (Box-folder 76: 73-1256)
    - William B. Saxbe, Attorney General of the United States v. Washington Post Co. (Box-folder 76: 73-1265)
      See also cases 73-754, and 73-918
    - Eugene C. Kelley v. Southern Pacific Company (Box-folder 76: 73-1270)
    - Williams & Wilkins Company v. United States (Box-folder 76: 73-1279)
    - John P. Wood v. Peggy Strickland, a Minor, by Mr. and Mrs. Virgil Justice, Her Parents and Next Friends (Box-folder 76: 73-1285)
    - United States v. ITT Continental Baking Company (Box-folder 76: 73-1290)
    - Jeffrey Cole Bigelow v. Commonwealth of Virginia (Box-folder X.: 73-1309)
    - International Telephone & Telegraph Corp., Communications Equipment & Systems Division v. Local 134, International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, AFL-CIO (Box-folder 77: 73-1313)
    - Renegotiation Board v. Grumman Aircraft Engineering Corporation (Box-folder 77: 73-1316)
    - John L. McLucas, Secretary of the Air Force v. Raymond G. DeChamplain (Box-folder 77: 73-1346)
    - Board of School Commissioners of the City of Indianapolis v. Jeff Jacobs (Box-folder X.: 73-1347)
    - National Labor Relations Board v. J. Weingarten, Inc. (Box-folder 77: 73-1363)
      See also case 73-765
    - Russell E. Train, Administrator, United States Environmental Protection Agency v. City of New York (Box-folder 77: 73-1377)
    - Russell E. Train, Administrator, United States Environmental Protection Agency v. Campaign Clean Water, Inc. (Box-folder 77: 73-1378)
    - Chemehuevi Tribe of Indians v. Federal Power Commission (Box-folder 77: 73-1380)
      See also cases 73-1666, and 73-1667
    - United States v. George J. Wilson, Jr. (Box-folder 77: 73-1395)
    - Daniel Chapman and Jacque Stockman v. Ben Meier (Box-folder 77: 73-1406)
    - David Emery Serfass v. United States (Box-folder 77: 73-1424)
    - Joan Roe, Peter Poe, and Coe Press Inc. v. Jane Doe (Box-folder 77: 73-1446)
    - State of Oregon v. William Robert Hass (Box-folder 77: 73-1452)
    - Thelma B. Stanton v. James Lawrence Stanton, Jr. (Box-folder 78: 73-1461)
    - Mark White v. Diana Regester (Box-folder 78: 73-1462)
    - United States v. New Jersey State Lottery Commission (Box-folder 78: 74-1471)
    - Harris County Commissioners Court v. Richard E. Moore (Box-folder 78: 73-1475)
    - Don R. Erickson v. John Lee Feather (Box-folder 78: 73-1500)
      Found in case 73-1148
    - United States v. Ronald S. Jenkins, (2 folders) (Box-folder 78: 73-1513)
    - Albert Johnson v. State of Mississippi (Box-folder 78: 73-1531)
    - Robert Reid and Nadia Alice Reid v. Immigration and Naturalization Service (Box-folder 78: 73-1541)
    - Willie Johnson, Jr. v. Railway Express Agency, Inc. (Box-folder 79: 73-1543)
    - Harold Withrow v. Duane Larkin (Box-folder 79: 73-1573)
    - Colonial Pipeline Company v. Joseph N. Triangle, Collector of Revenue (Box-folder 79: 73-1595)
    - Louis J. Lefkowitz, Attorney General of New York v. Leon Newsome (Box-folder 79: 73-1627)
    - Arizona Public Service Company v. Chemehuevi Tribe of Indians (Box-folder 79: 73-1666)
      Found in case 73-1380. See also cases 73-1380, and 73-1667.
    - Federal Power Commission v. Chemehuevi Tribe of Indians (Box-folder 79: 73-1667)
    - United States v. American Building Maintenance Industries (Box-folder 79: 73-1689)
    - Standard Pressed Steel Co. v. State of Washington Department of Revenue (Box-folder 79: 73-1697)
    - United States v. National Association of Securities Dealers, Inc. (Box-folder 79: 73-1701)
    - Kevin J. Burns v. Linda Alcala (Box-folder 79: 73-1708)
    - John L. Hill, Attorney General of Texas v. Michael L. Stone (Box-folder 79: 73-1723)
    - W. M. Gurley, dba Gurley Oil Company v. Arny Rhoden (Box-folder 79: 73-1734)
    - Russell E. Train, Administrator, United States Environmental Protection Agency v. Natural Resources Defense Council, Inc. (Box-folder 80: 73-1742)
    - Sylvia Meek v. John C. Pittenger (Box-folder 80: 73-1765)
    - Earl R. Foster v. Dravo Corporation (Box-folder 80: 73-1773)
    - United States v. American Friends Service Committee (Box-folder 80: 73-1791)
    - Paul R. Philbrook v. Jean Glodgett (Box-folder 80: 73-1820)
      See also case 74-132
    - United States v. State of Alaska (Box-folder 80: 73-1888)
    - Caspar W. Weinberger, Secretary of Health, Education, and Welfare v. Stephen Charles Wiesenfeld (Box-folder 80: 73-1892)
    - Stewart S. Cort v. Richard A. Ash (Box-folder 81: 73-1908)
    - James O. Eastland v. United States Servicemen's Fund (Box-folder 81: 73-1923)
    - James R. Muniz v. Roy O. Hoffman, Director, Region 20, National Labor Relations Board (Box-folder 81: 73-1924)
    - United States v. Citizens and Southern National Bank (Box-folder 81: 73-1933)
    - Richard Erznoznik v. City of Jacksonville (Box-folder 81: 73-1942)
    - Aberdeen and Rockfish Railroad Company v. Students Challenging Regulatory Agency Procedures (S.C.R.A.P.) (Box-folder X.: 73-1966)
      See also 73-1971
    - United States v. Students Challenging Regulatory Agency Procedures (S.C.R.A.P.) (Box-folder X.: 73-1971)
      Found in file 73-1966
    - Alyeska Pipeline Services Company v. Wilderness Society (Box-folder X.: 73-1977)
    - Julian Vella v. Ford Motor Company (Box-folder 81: 73-1994)
    - Allen F. Breed v. Gary Steven Jones (Box-folder 81: 73-1995)
    - United States v. James Robert Peltier (Box-folder 81: 73-2000)
    - Robert Warth v. Ira Seldin (Box-folder 81: 73-2024)
    - United States v. Luis Antonio Ortiz (Box-folder 82: 73-2050)
      See also cases 73-6848, and 74-114
    - Securities Investor Protection Corporation v. James C. Barbour (Box-folder 82: 73-2055)
    - Carl M. Austin v. State of New Hampshire (Box-folder Y.: 73-2060)
    - Annie Taylor v. Abe Lavine (Box-folder 82: 73-5054)
      Found in case 73-453
    - Margaret Mae Cantrell v. Forest City Publishing Co. (Box-folder 82: 73-5520)
    - Maurice Schick v. George J. Reed, Chairman of the United States Board of Parole (Box-folder 82: 73-5677)
    - Billy J. Taylor v. State of Louisiana (Box-folder 82: 73-5744)
    - Frank Xavier Francisco v. J. S. Gathright, Superintendent, Bland Correctional Farm (Box-folder 82: 73-5768)
    - Anthony Pasquale Faretta v. State of California (Box-folder 82: 73-5772)
    - Catherine Jackson v. Metropolitan Edison Company (Box-folder 82: 73-5845)
    - John E. Test v. United States (Box-folder 82: 73-5993)
    - Sharon Roe v. Nicholas Norton (Box-folder 82: 73-6033)
    - James Edward Drope v. State of Missouri (Box-folder 82: 73-6038)
    - George Herman Rogers v. United States (Box-folder 82: 73-6336)
    - Clifford Herring v. State of New York (Box-folder 83: 73-6587)
    - Richard Brown v. State of Illinois (Box-folder 83: 73-6650)
    - Steven Costarelli v. Commonwealth of Massachusetts (Box-folder 83: 73-6739)
    - John Lee Bowen v. United States (Box-folder 83: 73-6848)
      Found in cases 73-2050, and 74-114
    - John Lee Bowen v. United States (Box-folder Y.: 73-6848)
    - J. B. O'Connor v. Kenneth Donaldson (Box-folder 83: 74-8)
    - Garrell S. Mullaney v. Stillman E. Wilbur (Box-folder 83: 74-13)
    - Ivan Allen Company v. United States (Box-folder 83: 74-22)
    - Lewis H. Goldfarb v. Virginia State Bar (Box-folder 83: 74-70)
    - George F. Kugler, Jr. v. Edwin H. Helfant (Box-folder 83: 74-80)
      See also case 74-277
    - Peter Preiser v. James Newkirk (Box-folder 84: 74-107)
    - United States v. Felix Humberto Brignoni-Ponce. See cases 73-2050, and 73-6848 (Box-folder 84: 74-114)
    - Craig Phelps, Receiver in Bankruptcy v. United States (Box-folder 84: 74-121)
    - Blue Chip Stamps v. Manor Drug Stores (Box-folder Y.: 74-124)
    - Caspar W. Weinberger, Secretary of Health, Education, and Welfare v. Jean Glodgett (Box-folder 84: 74-132)
      Found in case 73-1820
    - Cecil Hicks, District Attorney of the County of Orange, State of California v. Vincent Miranda, dba Walnut Properties (Box-folder 84: 74-156)
    - United Housing Foundation, Inc. v. Milton Forman (Box-folder 84: 74-157)
      See also case 74-647
    - Robert W. Blanchette et al, as Trustees of Property of Penn Central Transportation Company v. Connecticut General Insurance Corporation (Box-folder Y.: 74-165)
      See also 74-166, 74-167, and 74-168
    - Richard Joyes Smith, Trustee of the Property of the New York, New Haven and Hartford Railroad Company v. United States (Box-folder Y.: 74-166)
      Found in file 74-165
    - United States Railway Association v. Connecticut General Insurance Corporation (Box-folder Y.: 74-167)
    - United States Railway Association v. Connecticut General Insurance Corporation (Box-folder 84: 74-167)
    - City of Richmond, Virginia v. United States (Box-folder 84: 74-201)
    - Caspar Weinberger, Secretary of Health, Education, and Welfare v. Kinsella Salfi, (2 folders) (Box-folder 84: 74-214)
    - United States v. John R. Park (Box-folder 84: 74-215)
    - Edwin H. Helfant v. George F. Kugler, Jr. (Box-folder 85: 74-277)
      Found in case 74-80
    - Richard A. Gordon v. New York Stock Exchange (Box-folder 85: 74-304)
    - Frank Doran v. Salem Inn, Inc. (Box-folder 85: 74-337)
    - Intercounty Construction Corporation v. Noah C. A. Walter (Box-folder 85: 74-362)
    - United States v. Reliable Transfer Co., Inc. (Box-folder 85: 74-363)
    - United States v. William G. Hale (Box-folder 85: 74-364)
    - Albemarle Paper Company v. Joseph P. Moody (Box-folder Y.: 74-389)
      See also 74-428
    - Administrator, Federal Aviation Administration v. Reuben B. Robertson, III (Box-folder 85: 74-450)
    - Twentieth Century Music Corporation v. George Aiken (Box-folder 85: 74-452)
    - John Hill, Attorney General of Texas v. Printing Industries of the Gulf Coast (Box-folder 85: 74-456)
    - John T. Dunlop, Secretary of Labor v. Walter Bachowski (Box-folder 85: 74-466)
    - W. J. Estelle, Jr., Director, Texas Department of Corrections v. Jerry Mack Dorrough (Box-folder 86: 74-479)
    - Commonwealth of Virginia v. United States (Box-folder 86: 74-481)
    - United States v. State Tax Commission of the State of Mississippi (Box-folder 86: 74-548)
    - United States v. Robert Lee Nobles (Box-folder 86: 74-634)
    - State of New York and the New York State Housing Finance Agency v. Milton Forman (Box-folder 86: 74-647)
      Found in case 74-157
    - Westby. v. Jane Doe (Box-folder 86: 74-684)
    - Clarence Brown v. General Services Administration (Box-folder 86: 74-768)
    - Scott Hudgens v. National Labor Relations Board (Box-folder 86: 74-773)
    - City of New Orleans v. Nancy Dukes, Louisiana Concessions (Box-folder 86: 74-775)
    - Thomas U. Greer, Commander, Fort Dix Military Reservation v. Benjamin Spock (Box-folder 86: 74-848)
    - F. David Mathews, Secretary of Health, Education, and Welfare v. William G. Weber (Box-folder 86: 74-850)
    - Hugh L. Carey, Governor of the State of New York v. Bert Randolph Sugar and Wrestling Revue, Inc. (Box-folder 87: 74-858)
      See also case 74-859
    - Curtis Circulation Company and Continental Casualty Company v. Bert Randolph Sugar and Wrestling Revue, Inc. (Box-folder 87: 74-859)
      Found in case 74-858
    - National League of Cities v. W. J. Usery, Jr., Secretary of Labor (Box-folder 87: 74-878)
      See also case 74-879
    - California v. Dunlop and State of California v. W. J. Usery, Jr., Secretary of Labor (Box-folder 87: 74-879)
      See also case 74-878
    - Mary Akin v. United States (Box-folder 87: 74-949)
    - Dallas County, Alabama v. F. D. Reese (Box-folder 87: 74-1077)
    - Peter J. Pitchess, Sheriff of Los Angeles County v. Charles Edward Davis (Box-folder 87: 74-1128)
    - Jack Roland Murphy v. State of Florida (Box-folder 87: 74-5116)
    - Michael J. Cassius v. State of Arizona (Box-folder 87: 74-5140)
- U.S. Supreme Court Opinions and Syllabi, 1971-2004
  Printed copies of opinions written by Rehnquist and printed copies of case syllabi, a short summary of the legal basis of a court's decision appearing at the beginning of a reported case. Some materials are bound. Arranged by October term.
  - Opinions, 1971-2004
    - Ten most important Rehnquist opinions (Box 88)
    - 1971 (Box 88)
    - 1972 (Box 88)
    - 1973 (Box 89)
    - 1974 (Box 89)
    - 1975 (Box 89)
    - 1976 (Box 89)
    - 1977 (Box 90)
    - 1978 (Box 90)
    - 1979 (Box 90)
    - 1980 (Box 90)
    - 1981 (Box 91)
    - 1982 (Box 91)
    - 1983 (Box 91)
    - 1984 (Box 91)
    - 1985 (Box 92)
    - 1986 (Box 92)
    - 1987 (Box 92)
    - 1988 (Box 92)
    - 1989 (Box 92)
    - 1990 (Box 92)
    - 1991 (Box 92)
    - 1992 (Box 93)
    - 1993 (Box 93)
    - 1994 (Box 93)
    - 1995 (Box 93)
    - 1996 (Box 93)
    - 1998 (Box 93)
    - 2000
      - Margaret Bagley v. John W. Byrd, Jr. (Box-folder 94: 01A236)
      - Ohio v. Matthew Reiner (Box-folder 94: 00-1028)
      - Major League Baseball Players Association v. Steve Garvey (Box-folder 94: 00-1210)
      - City of Elkhart v. William A. Books (Box-folder 94: 00-1407)
    - Gary O. Bartlett v. Ashley Stephenson, 2001 (Box-folder 94: 01A848)
    - 2003
      - Wisconsin Right to Life, Inc. v. Federal Election Commission (Box-folder 94: 04A194)
      - Betty Mitchell v. Gregory Esparza (Box-folder 94: 02-1369)
      - Clyde Timothy Bunkley v. Florida (Box-folder 94: 02-8636)
      - Illinois v. Gregory Fisher (Box-folder 94: 03-374)
      - Colorado General Assembly v. Ken Salazar, Attorney General of Colorado (Box-folder 94: 03-1082)
    - Rochelle Brosseau v. Kenneth J. Haugen, 2004 (Box-folder 94: 03-1261)
  - Syllabi, 1987-2004
    Arranged by October Term
    - 1987
      - Boyle, personal representative of the heirs and estate of Boyle v. United Technologies Corp. (Box-folder 94: 86-492)
      - Murray v. United States (Box-folder 94: 86-995)
      - Pierce, Secretary of Housing and Urban Development v. Underwood (Box-folder 94: 86-1512)
      - United States v. Kozminski (Box-folder 94: 86-2000)
      - Coy v. Iowa (Box-folder 94: 86-6757)
      - Frisby v. Schultz (Box-folder 94: 87-168)
      - Bowen, Secretary of Health and Human Services v. Kendrick (Box-folder 94: 87-253)
      - Roley, District Attorney of the Tenth Prosecutorial District of North Carolina v. National Federation of the Blind of North Carolina, Inc. (Box-folder 94: 87-328)
      - Communications Workers of America v. Beck (Box-folder 94: 87-637)
      - Bowen, Secretary of Health and Human Services v. Massachusetts (Box-folder 94: 87-712)
      - Morrison, Independent Counsel v. Olson (Box-folder 94: 87-1279)
      - Watson v. Fort Worth Bank & Trust (Box-folder 94: 87-6139)
    - 2000
      - Lujan, Labor Commissioner of California v. G&G Fire Sprinklers, Inc. (Box-folder 94: 00-152)
      - Idaho v. United States (Box-folder 94: 00-189)
      - Florida v. Thomas (Box-folder 94: 00-391)
      - Atkinson Trading Co., Inc. v. Shirley (Box-folder 94: 00-454)
      - George W. Bush v. Palm Beach County Canvassing Board (Box-folder 94: 00-836)
      - George W. Bush v. Albert Gore, Jr. (Box-folder 94: 00-949)
      - Cook v. Gralike (Box-folder 94: 99-929)
      - City of Indianapolis v. Edmond (Box-folder 94: 99-1030)
      - Solid Waste Agency of Northern Cook County v. United States Army Corps of Engineers (Box-folder 94: 99-1178)
      - Green Tree Financial Corp.-Alabama v. Randolph (Box-folder 94: 99-1235)
      - Board of Trustees of the University of Alabama v. Garrett (Box-folder 94: 99-1240)
      - Bartnicki v. Vopper, AKA Williams (Box-folder 94: 99-1687)
      - Texas v. Cobb (Box-folder 94: 99-1702)
      - Buckman Co. v. Plaintiffs' Legal Committee (Box-folder 94: 99-1768)
      - Buckhannon Board & Care Home, Inc. v. West Virginia Department of Health and Human Resources (Box-folder 94: 99-1848)
      - District of Columbia v. Tri County Industries, Inc. (Box-folder 94: 99-1953)
    - 2001
      - Adarand Constructors, Inc. v. Norman Y. Mineta, Secretary of Transportation (Box-folder 94: 00-730)
      - Ashcroft, Attorney General v. Free Speech Coalition (Box-folder 94: 00-795)
      - Tahoe-Sierra Preservation Council, Inc. v. Tahoe Regional Planning Agency (Box-folder 94: 00-1167)
      - United States v. Knights (Box-folder 94: 00-1260)
      - United States v. Arvizu (Box-folder 94: 00-1519)
      - Hoffman Plastic Compounds, Inc. v. National Labor Relations Board (Box-folder 94: 00-1595)
      - Department of Housing and Urban Development v. Rucker (Box-folder 94: 00-1770)
      - Watchtower Bible & Tract Society of New York, Inc. v. Village of Stratton (Box-folder 94: 00-1737)
      - Zelman, Superintendent of Public Instruction of Ohio v. Simmons-Harris (Box-folder 94: 00-1751)
      - Dusenbery v. United States (Box-folder 94: 00-6567)
      - Atkins v. Virginia (Box-folder 94: 00-8452)
      - Kelly v. South Carolina (Box-folder 94: 00-9280)
      - Bell v. Cone (Box-folder 94: 01-400)
      - Wanda Adams v. Florida Power Corporation and Florida Progress Corporation (Box-folder 94: 01-584)
      - United States v. Cotton (Box-folder 94: 01-687)
    - 2002
      - Syngenta Crop Protection, Inc. v. Henson (Box-folder 94: 01-757)
      - Ford Motor Company and Citibank (South Dakota), N. A. v. John B. McCauley (Box-folder 94: 01-896)
      - Scheidler v. National Organization for Women (Box-folder 94: 01-1118)
      - Connecticut Department of Public Safety v. Doe, Individually and on Behalf of All Others Similarly Situated (Box-folder 94: 01-1231)
      - Borden Ranch Partnership and Angelo K. Tsakopoulos v. United States Army Corps of Engineers and Environmental Protection Agency (Box-folder 94: 01-1243)
      - Nevada Department of Human Resources v. Hibbs (Box-folder 94: 01-1368)
      - Demore, District Director, San Francisco District of Immigration and Naturalization Service v. Kim (Box-folder 94: 01-1491)
      - Abu-Ali Abdur'rahman v. Ricky Bell (Box-folder 94: 01-9094)
      - Nguyen v. United States (Box-folder 94: 01-10873)
      - Grutter v. Bollinger (Box-folder 94: 02-241)
      - Dow Chemical Company v. Daniel Raymond Stephenson (Box-folder 94: 02-271)
      - United States v. American Library Association (Box-folder 94: 02-361)
      - Gratz v. Bollinger (Box-folder 94: 02-516)
      - Price v. Vincent (Box-folder 94: 02-524)
      - Nike, Inc. v. Marc Kasky (Box-folder 94: 02-575)
      - Green Tree Financial Corp., NKA Conseco Finance Corp. v. Bazzle ET AL., In a Representative Capacity on Behalf of a Class and for All Others Similarly Situated (Box-folder 94: 02-634)
    - 2003
      - Virginia v. Maryland (Box-folder 94: 129 Original)
      - Maryland v. Pringle (Box-folder 94: 02-809)
      - Locke, Governor of Washington v. Davey (Box-folder 94: 02-1315)
      - Tennessee Student Assistance Corporation v. Hood (Box-folder 94: 02-1606)
      - Elk Grove Unified School Disctrict v. Newdow (Box-folder 94: 02-1624)
      - Tennessee v. Lane (Box-folder 94: 02-1667)
      - McConnell, United States Senator v. Federal Election Commission (Box-folder 94: 02-1674)
      - United States v. Flores-Montano (Box-folder 94: 02-1794)
      - Shakur Muhammad, AKA John Mease v. Mark Close (Box-folder 94: 02-9065)
      - Crawford v. Washington (Box-folder 94: 02-9410)
      - Rumsfeld, Secretary of Defense v. Padilla (Box-folder 94: 03-1027)
      - Thornton v. United States (Box-folder 94: 03-5165)
      - Jay Shawn Johnson v. California (Box-folder 94: 03-6539)
    - 2004
      - Ballard v. Commissioner of Internal Revenue (Box-folder 94: 03-184)
      - Kowalski, Judge 26th Judicial Circuit Court of Michigan v. Tesmer (Box-folder 94: 03-407)
      - Leocal v. Ashcroft, Attorney General (Box-folder 94: 03-583)
      - Tenet v. Doe (Box-folder 94: 03-1395)
      - Muehler v. Mena (Box-folder 94: 03-1423)
      - Van Orden v. Perry, In His Official Capacity as Governor of Texas and Chairman, State Preservation Board (Box-folder 94: 03-1500)
      - Marlon Latodd Howell, AKA Marlon Cox v. Mississippi (Box-folder 94: 03-9560)
      - Pace v. DiGuglielmo, Superintendent, State Correctional Institution at Graterford (Box-folder 94: 03-9627)
      - San Remo Hotel, L. P., v. City and County of San Francisco, California (Box-folder 94: 04-340)
      - Arthur Andersen LLP v. United States (Box-folder 94: 04-368)
      - Jose Ernesto Medellin v. Doug Dretke, Director, Texas Department of Criminal Justice, Correctional Institutions Division (Box-folder 94: 04-5928)
- Correspondence, 1969-2005
  Consists of both official and personal correspondence, dating from Justice Rehnquist's appointment to the Supreme Court until just before his death in 2005. The bulk of the correspondence concerns routine matters pertaining to Rehnquist's work schedule, his travel plans, and speaking engagements. The series also contains journal articles sent to Justice Rehnquist by legal scholars. The correspondence does not concern matters before the Supreme Court, nor does it contain substantive expositions of Justice Rehnquist's judicial philosophy. The finding aid indicates places (boxes 139, 144, and 171) where there is correspondence to and from other Supreme Court justices, again of a routine or personal nature.
  At the beginning of the series there are a large number of letters of condolence sent to Justice Rehnquist on the occasion of his wife's death, as well as a separate grouping of letters of congratulation sent to him upon his appointment as Chief Justice. There is also a small amount of family correspondence at the end of the series.